[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This river flows through the southern part of England and passes through the capital of the country.", "correct_answer": "The Thames", "incorrect_answers": ["The Avon", "All of these", "The Mersey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following statements is true about vitamin C, which is found mostly in citrus fruit and berries?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["It keeps blood vessels healthy.", "It prevents hair loss.", "It improves blood circulations to the scalp."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Fast Times at Ridgemont High, at what restaurant did Stacy and Linda work?", "correct_answer": "Perrys Pizza", "incorrect_answers": ["Captain Hooks Fish and Chips", "Bronco Burger", "All-American Burger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of interesting noise are cockroaches known to produce when they feel threatened?", "correct_answer": "Hissing", "incorrect_answers": ["Crackling", "Whistling", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1988 movie is this quote from: Outside the limit of our sight, feeding off us, perched on top of us, from birth to death, are our owners! Our owners!?", "correct_answer": "They Live", "incorrect_answers": ["Hellraiser", "The Gate", "The Hills Have Eyes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Malcolm McLaren and Vivienne Westwood had a famous boutique in London whose name was often changed through the years. Which of these is not one of the boutiques names?", "correct_answer": "God Save the Queen", "incorrect_answers": ["Seditionaries", "Sex", "Too Fast to Live, Too Young to Die"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Carbohydrates can be found in breads, cereals, fruits, and vegetables. Which of these compounds is not a carbohydrate?", "correct_answer": "Glycerol", "incorrect_answers": ["Fructose", "Cellulose", "Starch"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1981 movie is this quote from:  Soon all of you will be like me... And then who will lock you up in a cellar??", "correct_answer": "The Evil Dead", "incorrect_answers": ["The Last House on the Left", "The Hills Have Eyes", "The Texas Chainsaw Massacre"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed Vietnam War veteran Ron Kovic in Oliver Stones 1989 movie Born on the Fourth of July?", "correct_answer": "Tom Cruise", "incorrect_answers": ["Christopher Walken", "Dustin Hoffman", "Sean Penn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The companies Intel and AMD are primarily known for their development and manufacturing of what?", "correct_answer": "Processors", "incorrect_answers": ["Video Cards", "Software", "Ram"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Were Tom Laughlin and Delores Taylor married when they starred in the Billy Jack movies?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the first womens college in the USA?", "correct_answer": "Mt. Holyoke", "incorrect_answers": ["Radcliffe", "Douglas", "Bryn Mawr"]}]